Guide to the Larry Racioppo Photograph Collection 1989-2017 PR 208
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Photographs from The Word on the Street: The Photographs of Larry Racioppo, 1990-2005; 2 Linear feet
  Mt. Kinley Square Theater, Boston Road, Bronx, NYC, 1999, 30x40; McKinley Square Theater (burned interior) Boston Road, Bronx, NYC, 1999, 30x40
  Doorway to Hell, Fulton Street near Rockaway Avenue, Brooklyn, 2001, 30x40
  Valencia Theater, Tabernacle of Prayer, Jamaica Avenue, Queens, NYC, 1999, 30x40; Valencia Theater (interior with cross), Tabernacle of Prayer, Jamaica Avenue, 1999, 30x40
  Pablo's Cross, Rockaway Beach Boulevard and Beach 47th Street, Queens, 1994, 17x51, mounted on Dibond
  Series IV is arranged by size.
  Gift of Bruce Berman and Lea Russo, 2016 (accession no. PPAC-2016-47).
  Credit line: Bruce Berman and Lea Russo.
  - 16x20 photos, 1990-1996 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 20x24 photos, 1992-2005 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 30x40 photos, 1998-2001 (Folder FF 1)
  - 17x51 photo mounted on Dibond, 1994 (Folder FF 2)
- Series V: Chapbooks, 2017; 0.209 Linear feet
  Four chapbooks (approximately 7.5 x 7.5) of photographs taken by Racioppo. Images from Grace: Photographs of NYC Churches are also present in the collection as prints in Series II: New York City Churches.
  - Believers, 2017 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
  - Good Friday in Brooklyn, 2017 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
  - Grace: Photographs of NYC Churches, 2017 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 4)
  - Ellis Island: the Polaroids, 2017 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 5)